这不是一个执行任务的模型。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: This is not
a model of jobs of execution.
每次我们有任务要做的时候，我们必须在继续前进之前完成它。
Every single time we have a task to do,
we must finish it before we move on.
但这会带来一个大问题。
But that's gonna pose a big problem.
单线程，一次一个命令，并执行同步性。
Single threaded, one command at a time,
and synchronicity executed.
这意味着在你移动到下一行之前，每一行都必须完成。
That means each line must be finished
before you move onto the next line.
但这可能会产生一个问题。
But that might create a problem.
如果我们有一个任务，比如对服务器说话,
What if we have a task
like speaking to a server,
的服务器，获取新的 tweets。
to Twitter's server, to get new tweets.
点击这里查看 Twitter 上的新消息,
To like we click here to
view new tweets on Twitter,
它会向 Twitter 的服务器发送一条消息。
it's gonna send a message
to Twitter's server.
关于这些信息从推特上传回来的数据,
And on those messages,
the data coming back from Twitter,
然后想要显示新的数据，那些新的 tweets。
is then going to want to display
that new data, those new tweets.
我们必须坐在那条线上，等待数据回来，当数据回来的时候
We've gotta sit on that line, and wait for
that data to come back, and when it comes
最后回来，然后我们可以显示它，然后我们可以继续下一行。
back finally, then we can display it, and
then we can move on to the next line.
但那可能需要半秒钟，可能需要更长时间,
But that could take like half a second,
it could take longer,
在那段时间里，我们不能再运行任何代码了。
and in that time we can't run
any further code afterwards.
这是一个严重的问题。
That's a serious problem.
我们想要等待
We want to wait for
将 tweets 存储在 tweets 中，而不是运行一个函数。
the tweets to be stored in tweets as
opposed to be sort of, run a function.
让我们看看。那么,
Let's have a look.
So,
如果你曾经运行过 get tweets 这样的函数，它会向 Twitter 发送一条消息。
if you ever run a function like get
tweets, it sends off a message to Twitter.
推特回来后我们会把它们存在标签推特里,
And when the tweets come back, we're
gonna store them in the label tweets,
然后我们要把这些推文。
then we're gonna display those tweets.
但与此同时，我们是否可以进一步讨论下面的代码？
But in the meantime,
can we move on to any further code below?
不，不是在 JavaScript 中，不是在我们现在的 JavaScript 模型中。
No, not in JavaScript,
not with our current model of JavaScript.
想象一下这样做的后果，比如假设我正在做一件松弛的事情
And imagine what that does,
like suppose I'm doing on a slack
比如我点击表情符号，然后点击表情符号回复。
like I'm clicking emoji, and
then clicking emoji responses.
我们的最爱。
Our favorite.
所以点击表情符号回复，它就会发送一条信息到
So clicking emoji responses,
and it's sending a message to
懒散地说嘿，新的表情符号灯。
slack saying hey, new emoji light.
在得到确认之前它不能继续前进,
It can't move on until it's
got confirmation back,
已经成功更新到服务器上了。
that that was successfully
updated to the server.
在确认代码之前，您不能转移到进一步的代码。
You can't kinda move onto to further
code until you've confirmed its code.
理论上是这样的，对吧？
Well, in theory, right?
然后意味着如果你试图点击下一个表情符号回复，和
And then meaning if you're trying to
click the next emoji response, and
七个都排好了你要喜欢每一个,
you got the seven lined up, and
you need to like every single one,
因为它是非常，娱乐性的信息，你点击每一个。
because it is very, entertaining message,
you click each one.
你无法点击下一个,
You wouldn't be able
to click the next one,
直到你确认前一个被点击了。
until you got confirmation back of
the previous one being clicked.
如果你在 Twitter 上，并且
If you're on Twitter, and
你点击查看更多的推文，它会发送一条消息，说嘿，得到新的推文。
you click view more tweets, it's gonna
send a message say hey, get new tweets.
把他们带回来，直到你收到他们的推文，你才能继续前进
Bring them back, and until you get
the tweets back, you can't move on and
点击页面上的其他东西。
click any other stuff on the page.
你点击一个心形喜欢一个表情符号，然后在它回来之前喜欢一条推特,
You click a heart to like an emoji,
and like a tweet before it comes back,
你点击那个心脏却没有任何反应,
you click that heart, and
you're getting no response,
因为这个代码需要运行，才能把心脏从透明变成粉红色。
because that's code that needs to run
to turn the heart from clear to pink.
那我们该怎么办？
So, what are we gonna do?
慢的函数阻碍了进一步的代码运行，所以，我们能做什么人呢？
Slow function blocks further code
running so, what can we do people?
让我们把它变得更难。
Let's make it even harder.
如果我们想直接延迟函数的运行，使用 set timer,
What if we wanted to directly delay
a function running, using set timer,
内置功能？
built in function?
它的第一个输入，是你想延迟运行的函数。
Its first input,
is the function you wanna delay running.
它的第二个输入，是你想延迟的毫秒数。
And its second input, is the number of
milliseconds by which you wanna delay it.
所以，对于 Ethan，很高兴你们都回来了
So, to Ethan, it's lovely to have all
of you back by the way to, and for
我们的在线观众稍后会以视频的形式观看,
our online audience who are watching
this in a video format later,
从今天早些时候开始 Ethan,
from earlier today from
this one day world, Ethan,
现在暂停会怎么样？
what are we gonna have happen
here with this set timeout?
所以我有我的功能打印你好。
So I've got my function print hello.
我已经设置了一个超时调用，打印 hello，1000毫秒延迟。
I've got my set timeout call with
print hello, 1000 milliseconds delay.
假设我必须在设定暂停时间内完成，对吧，在那之前？
Presume I gotta do it inside set timeout,
right, before I then have?
我们现有的 JavaScript 模型会以什么顺序
In what order, Ethan, would our
existing model of JavaScript suggest
控制台日志会发生。
the console logs would happen.
那么你认为这是真实发生的吗？
And then do you think that's
actually what happens?
把它拿走，伊森。
Take it away Ethan.
伊森: 我想你会等一会儿，然后
&gt;&gt; Ethan: I think you'll wait for
one second, and
然后打印你好，然后你会先打印我。
then print hello, and
then you'll print me first.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 我的意思是，如果你看看我在这里得到了什么，这是一种解释
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I mean, if you look at
what I've got here, that's kind of explain
不然怎么能举起手来呢，不要在这里举手。
how else it could be and yet raise,
no raising hands from here and yet.
我们认为这是真实发生的吗？
Do we think that's actually what happens?
不可能。
There's no way.
但是对于我们现有的 JavaScript 模型，Ethan 是正确的。
But with our existing model of JavaScript,
Ethan would be spot on.
让我们把它变得更加极端。
Let's make it even more extreme.
这里是布雷登，现在我们已经得到了零毫秒的延迟。
Brayden here, now we've got
delay at zero milliseconds now.
现在，我假设，现在我假设它会很好。
Now, I assume,
now I assume it will be fine.
布雷登，你觉得控制台日志的顺序是怎样的？
Brayden, what's that order of
console logs here, do you think?
布雷登: 和以前一样，我们在那里打招呼，然后
&gt;&gt; Brayden: The same as before,
where we'd say hello, and
那么它指的是威尔 · 森坦斯: 不是那样的
then it refers to
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It wasn't that
以前也是。
before, either.
布雷登: 如果你遵循
[LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Brayden: If you follow the, [LAUGH]
威尔 · 森特斯: 好吧，我们走
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Okay, let's
看看我们到底在想什么。
see what we actually think.
所以之前，实际上，是的。
So before, actually, it was, yeah.
先是我，然后是你好。
Me first, and then hello.
我们觉得这样不对吗？
We didn't feel like that'd be right?
但是我们知道在现实中，先是接近我，然后是你好,
But we know in reality is closer
towards me first, and then hello,
但这说不通啊。
but that makes no sense.
你觉得布雷登怎么样？
So here, what do you think Brayden?
布雷登: 在你好第一，没有等待。
&gt;&gt; Brayden: In hello first,
there's no wait.
那样更符合逻辑，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That would
be more logical right?
他说的对吗？
Is he right?
这就是为什么答案是否定的。
That's why the answer's no.
布雷登: (笑)威尔 · 森坦斯: 他，不是,
&gt;&gt; Brayden: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: He's, not,
我先来。
it's gonna be me first.
然后你好。
And then hello.
这是什么语言？
What is this language?
这是深刻的。
This is profound.
因为在现实中，仅有 JavaScript 是不够的。
For in reality, JavaScript is not enough.
我们需要新的代码，其中一些根本不是 JavaScript,
We need new pieces, some of which
aren't actually JavaScript at all,
为了解释这里发生了什么，我们的核心 Java 引擎，我们已经看到了一切。
in order to explain what's happening here,
our core Java engine, we've seen it all.
它有三个主要部分。
It has three main parts.
实际上，让我们确保我们的调用堆栈在这里。
Actually, let's make sure
our call stack is on here.
它有三个主要部分。
It has three main parts.
它拥有我们的记忆，存储东西，我们的执行线程。
It has our memory, storing stuff,
our thread of execution.
执行上下文，它只是基于这两个东西的迷你版本。
Execution context, that has been based on
just mini versions of those two things.
它有我们的调用堆栈，全局总是在底部。
And it has our call stack on which
global is always at the bottom.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 用这个模型，我们乘以二,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: With the model,
that and we have multiplied by two,
当我们在这里经营的时候。
when we're running it here.
我们在全球范围内取下它，我们在这里运行它，它在顶端。
We take it off throughout the global
we run it here, it's on top.
这些都是 JavaScript 但是我们需要添加新的组件,
This is all a JavaScript but,
we're gonna have to add new components,
我们得加上。
we're gonna have to add.
网页浏览器的功能，我们必须加上承诺。
Web browser features,
we have to add promises.
事件循环回调任务、回调任务和微任务队列。
The event loop callback task, callback
will task you, and the microtask queue.
我们要把这些加到我们的拼图中，来解释什么是
And we're gonna add all of these to
our puzzle in order to explain what's
发生在这里。
happening here.